socialhp.com 2019-01-15

# SocialHP: Organize Your Team, Get Results

Last Updated: March 29th, 2018

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SocialHP.com Media Inc. (the "Company", "we", "us" or "our") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") in connection with the access to or use of the Service. This Privacy Policy applies to the Service and all products and services offered by the Company. Accessing or using our Service signifies the acceptance to abide by the terms stipulated in this Privacy Policy.

The Privacy Policy is a part of our Terms of Use and is incorporated therein by references.

### What Types of Information We Collect

When you use our Service, we may collect two types of information:

### Personal Information

The Personal Information we collect (i.e. information that may allow the identification of the User) includes information voluntarily submitted by the User, including the Users' name and email address, phone number, billing address and certain payment information (e.g. credit card's expiration date and last four digits, etc.). We may also collect Personal Information from your device, such as your IP address.

### Non-Personal Information

Non-Personal Information may include the browser name, the type of the User's device and technical information transmitted by the User's device, language preferences, time stamps and visited pages, the operating system, utilized internet service provider and other similar information. We may also collect the User's IP address which would be irrevocably anonymized.

### How We Collect Your Information?

  * When the User voluntarily submits Personal Information (by filling out a form, subscribing to our newsletter, responding to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available in connection with our Service); Users may always refuse to provide Personal Information.
  * Non-Personal Information may be automatically transmitted by the User's device.
  * When using our Service we assign the User's device with a log file, a cookie (session or persistent), web beacons or other related technologies, to collect Non-Personal Information with respect to the User's activity on our Service.
  * A "cookie" is a small piece of information that a website assigns to your device while you are viewing a website. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, enable automatic activation of certain features, remembering your preferences and making the interaction between you and our services quicker and easier. Cookies are also used to help customize your experience. You can find more information about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org. You may remove our cookie by following the instructions of your device preferences; however, if you choose to disable our cookie, some features of our Service may not operate properly and your online experience may be limited.
  * We also use a tool called "Google Analytics" to collect information about your use of the Services. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users access the Services, what pages they visit when they do so, etc. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our Services. Google Analytics collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit sites, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.

### With Whom We Share Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' Personal Information to other parties. We may share Personal Information with our trusted service providers only to the extent required to fulfill the purposes outlined above. We will only provide our service providers the information which is reasonably required to perform the services, and they will be prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

We may also disclose Personal Information, or any other information submitted by a User via the Service if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our policies, including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) investigate, detect, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or other wrongdoing, suspected fraud or security issues; (iv) to establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims; (v) prevent harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our users, yourself or any third party; or (vi) for the purpose of collaborating with law enforcement agencies and/or in case we find it necessary in order to enforce intellectual property or other legal rights.

Non-Personal Information may be shared with other third parties (including retailers, ad networks, advertising companies, service providers, media and other interested parties) in any of the above circumstances, as well as for the purpose of developing or delivering advertising (whether via our Service, or websites, applications or services of third parties), or for the purpose of improving our Service, conducting business analysis or other business purposes. This information may be combined with information we collect from other sources, to the extent that the information remains Anonymous Information.

### Transfer of Personal Information from the EU

Since we operate globally, it may be necessary to transfer your Personal Information to countries outside of the European Union (EU).

The data protection and other laws of these countries may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union - in these instances we will take steps to ensure that a similar level of protection is given to your Personal Information.

You hereby consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to countries outside of the European Union.

### Retention Policy and User Rights

We respect your privacy rights and therefore you may contact us at info@socialhp.com at any time and request:

  * to access, delete, change or update any Personal Information relating to you (for example, if you believe that your Personal Information is incorrect, you may ask to have it corrected or deleted); or
  * that we will cease any further use of your Personal Information (for example, you may ask that we will stop using or sharing your Personal Information with third parties) or that we shall remove your Personal Information (subject to any other legal obligation that may require us to keep the information, such as transactional history and information which is required by anti-money laundering regulation).

We may rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your Personal Information, please contact our DPO at info@socialhp.com.

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are collecting or processing your Personal Information not in accordance with the laws, you can complain to the applicable data protection authority.

Unless we are instructed otherwise by Users, we retain the information we collect for a period of seven (7) years. We store the information to provide the Service and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

### Information on Minors

We will not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 16. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 16, we will remove its information from our servers. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that children are not using the Service.

### Security

We use industry standard security tools and measures, as well as internal guidelines and organizational procedures to prevent information misuse and data leakage. The information is also protected using Amazon's Web Services cloud-based computing and data storage infrastructure (Amazon S3). You may read more about how Amazon Web Services incorporates best practices concerning data security at this link: http://aws.amazon.com/security.

While we strive to use commercially acceptable means and procedures to protect the information, which considerably reduce the risks of data misuse, we cannot guarantee that our systems will be absolutely safe. If you become aware of any security vulnerability or potential data breach, please contact us immediately at info@socialhp.com, and we will take the appropriate measures to address such incident, as deemed necessary.

### Marketing

We may use your Personal Information, such as your name or email address, ourselves or by using our third party subcontractors for the purpose of providing you with promotional materials, concerning our Services, as well as products, services, websites and applications, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials.

If you have given us your consent, we may also send communications for unrelated products or services. In addition, we may elect to share your Personal Information with qualified third-party partners for marketing or other similar purposes but only where you agree to share such information. Such partners will be prohibited from disclosing or using such information except for the limited purposes which the users have consented to.

Out of respect to your right to privacy we provide you within such marketing materials with means to decline receiving further marketing offers from us. In addition, at any time, you may request to unsubscribe and discontinue receiving marketing offers by contacting by sending a blank message with the word "remove" to info@socialhp.com.

Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our mailing list, we may continue to send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical, service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, confirming you requested a product or service, or providing periodic updates or information relating to the product or service you requested.

### Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy

In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or other corporate transaction, or in the event of bankruptcy or a comparable event, we reserve the right to transfer or assign information, including Personal Information, in connection with the foregoing events. In the event of the above, our affiliated companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Service that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Service. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Service, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Amendment to the Privacy Policy

The Company has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage periodic review of our Privacy Policy for any changes in order to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. The last amendments will be reflected in the "Last Updated" heading. The continued use of the Service following the posting of any amendments will be deemed as acceptance of those amendments.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of our Service, please contact us by email at info@socialhp.com or by mail at 219 Dufferin Street Unit 18C, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, M6K 3J1 ATTN: Privacy Office, Legal.
